A Guide to the Webb-Prentis Family Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- SERIES I: CORRESPONDENCE
  - B. Joseph Prentis, Jr. and Family
    - Maggie Smith to Cousin Peter and Cousin Margaret, 1874-1878 (Box Box 12)
    - Robert N. Smith to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1812-1813 (Box Box 12)
    - John Southgate to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1810-1811 (Box Box 12)
    - Dr. Robert B. Stark to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1825-1829 (Box Box 12)
    - Lucy Swepson to Margaret Susan Prentis and Susan Caroline Prentis, 1821-1827 (Box Box 12)
    - Dr. Henry W. Tabb to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1849 (Box Box 12)
    - Richard Taylor to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1806-1811 (Box Box 12)
    - Gen. Robert B. Taylor to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1808-1833 (Box Box 12)
    - Tazewell Taylor to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1842-1848 (Box Box 12)
    - Littleton Tazewell to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1810-1822 (Box Box 12)
    - Billings Tisdale to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1816 (Box Box 12)
    - John Tunis to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1813-1829 (Box Box 12)
    - A. P. Upshur to Jospeh Prentis, Jr., 1813, 1841 (Box Box 12)
    - Van Antwerp and Dissoway to Thomas S. Shepherd and Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1834 (Box Box 12)
    - Daniel Vaughan to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1822 (Box Box 12)
    - Capt. Jacob Vickery to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1826-1840 (Box Box 12)
    - Samuel Vickery to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1818-1821 (Box Box 13)
    - Samuel Vickery to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1822-1834 (Box Box 13)
    - Frederick Vincent to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1829-1834 (Box Box 13)
    - William P. Vincent to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1834-1835 (Box Box 13)
    - Vincent and Butterworth to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1834 (Box Box 13)
    - Edward S. Waddey to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1815-1818 (Box Box 13)
    - William Walke to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1839 (Box Box 13)
    - John B. Walker to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1824 (Box Box 13)
    - John Augustine Washington to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1848 (Box Box 13)
    - George Webb to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1823-1824 (Box Box 13)
    - Joseph Prentis Webb to Dr. Robert Henning and Margaret Susan Prentis Webb, 1856-1865 (Box Box 13)
    - Lewis Webb to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1824-1834 (Box Box 13)
    - Margaret S. Prentis Webb to Susan C. Riddick Prentis, Mary Louisa Swepson, Marianna L. Prentis, and Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1822-1831 (Box Box 13)
    - Margaret S. Prentis Webb to Joseph Prentis, Jr., Susan C. Riddick Prentis, and Joseph C. Webb, 1833-1879 (Box Box 13)
    - Richard Daniel Webb to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1821-1832 (Box Box 14)
    - Robert Henning Webb (I) to Joseph Prentis, Jr. and Margaret Susan Prentis Webb, 1820-1866 (Box Box 14)
    - Robert Henning Webb (II) to Mrs. Joseph Prentis Webb, 1890-1893 (Box Box 14)
    - James Webster to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1816 (Box Box 14)
    - Wesson & Trask to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1836 (Box Box 14)
    - Benjamin White to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1827-1833 (Box Box 14)
    - Exum White to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1805-1812 (Box Box 14)
    - Joseph B. Whitehead to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1822-1828 (Box Box 14)
    - Dr. N. C. Whitehead to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1826-1828 (Box Box 14)
    - Samuel Whitehead to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1806-1810 (Box Box 14)
    - Swepson Whitehead to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1807-1828 (Box Box 14)
    - Charles Whitlock to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1816-1818 (Box Box 14)
    - Richard N. Whitlock to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1814-1837 (Box Box 14)
    - Dr. Willis Wilkinson to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1812-1821 (Box Box 14)
    - Holt Wilson to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1812-1826 (Box Box 14)
    - Samuel M. Wilson to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1842 (Box Box 14)
    - William H. Wilson to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1848 (Box Box 14)
    - Rev. John H. Wingfield to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1839-1847 (Box Box 14)
    - Col. Willis H. Woodley to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1829-1840 (Box Box 14)
    - Peter Wright to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1837 (Box Box 14)
    - James Young to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1818 (Box Box 14)
    - Dr. Robert W. Young to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1832 (Box Box 14)
    - Helen [ ? ] to [Joseph Prentis Webb], 1862-1865 (Box Box 14)
  - C. Prentis Family
    - Samuel Athawes to Robert Prentis, 1775, 1783 (Box Box 15)
    - Samuel Beall to William Prentis, 1778-1787 (Box Box 15)
    - John Blair to Robert Prentis, 1775-1779 (Box Box 15)
    - Carter Braxton to Robert Prentis, 1774-1785 (Box Box 15)
    - Osgood Hanbury to Robert Prentis, 1771 -1773 (Box Box 15)
    - James Holdcraft to Robert Prentis, 1778 (Box Box 15)
    - John Norton & Sons to John Prentis & Co., 1775, 1789 (Box Box 15)
    - Richard Wall to Robert Prentis, 1770 (Box Box 15)
    - Sarah Prentis Waters, 1776-1801 (Box Box 15)
    - Thomas Webb to Robert Prentis, 1778-1780 (Box Box 15)
    - William McKendre Watkins to Robert R. Prentis, [1855]-1905 (Box Box 15)
    - Letters to Robert Riddick Prentis II, 1879-1920 (Box Box 15)
  - D. Allen and Darden Families
    - Archibald Allen to William G. Driver; "Valuation and Division of Negroes belonging to the estate... ", 1828-1860 (Box Box 15)
    - Edward Archibald Allen to family; Obituary; Poems re freedom, 1908-1922, n.d. (Box Box 15)
    - Hannah Allen to Margaret S. Prentis, Archibald Allen, and Mary Allen, 1828-1860 (Box Box 15)
    - William Edward Allen to Algernon Sidney Darden, 1855 (Box Box 15)
    - Mary Allen Cook to Mary Swepson Allen Darden, 1855-1866 (Box Box 15)
    - Betty Swepson Diggs to Mary Swepson Darden Allen, 1847-1848 (Box Box 15)
    - W. W. Kennedy to Archibald and Mary Swepson Allen, 1844-1846 (Box Box 15)
    - Indiana Virginia Kilby to Mary Swepson and Lucy Allen, 1860 (Box Box 15)
    - Rev. B. B. Miles to Archibald Allen, 1836-1841 (Box Box 15)
    - Honoria O'Grady (Nony) to Mrs. Algernon Sidney Darden and Mrs. Mary Allen, 1846-1865 (Box Box 15)
    - J. H. Riddick to Mollie S. Allen, 1854 (Box Box 15)
    - Mary [Taylor] Riddick to Mrs. Mary Allen, 1847-1851 (Box Box 15)
    - E. H. Tompkins to Mary Swepson Allen, 1864, 1881 (Box Box 15)
    - Eliza Ann [Swepson] Whitlock to Mrs. Archibald Allen, 1826-1866 (Box Box 15)
    - Edward [ ? ] to Mary Swepson Allen, n.d. (Box Box 15)
    - Lizzie [ ? ] to Mary Swepson Allen, 1860 (Box Box 15)
  - E. MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE
    - Capt. James C. Causey to "My Dear friend", 1865 (Box Box 15)
    - Lord Dunmore to Treasurer of Virginia and J & R Drummond, 1772-1775 (Box Box 15)
    - Joseph P. Hall to Thomas S. Shepherd, 1834-1866 (Box Box 15)
    - Robert Hines to James Johnson, 1816-1822 (Box Box 15)
    - David Meade to John Driver, 1782-1796 (Box Box 15)
    - Col. Thomas Newton, Jr. to Benjamin Bartlett and Lemuel Riddick, 1789-1792 (Box Box 15)
    - George Nicolson to Mr. Robert Nicolson, 1787 (Box Box 15)
    - Jacob Vickery, Jr. to A. C. Withers, 1878 (Box Box 15)
    - Correspondence: A, 1805-1850 (Box Box 16)
    - Correspondence: B, 1776-1858 (Box Box 16)
    - Correspondence: C, 1757-1859 (Box Box 16)
    - Correspondence: D, 1805-1870 (Box Box 16)
    - Correspondence: E, 1806-1850 (Box Box 16)
    - Correspondence: F, 1770-1805 (Box Box 16)
    - Correspondence: G, 1808-1873 (Box Box 16)
    - Correspondence: H, 1774-1864 (Box Box 16)
    - Correspondence: J-K, 1806-1868 (Box Box 16)
    - Correspondence: L, 1805-1849 (Box Box 16)
    - Correspondence: Mc, 1805-1806 (Box Box 16)
    - Correspondence: M, 1786-1878 (Box Box 16)
    - Correspondence: N-O, 1788-1828 (Box Box 16)
    - Correspondence: P, 1783-1849 (Box Box 16)
    - Correspondence: R, 1787-1869 (Box Box 16)
    - Correspondence: S, 1783-1875 (Box Box 16)
    - Correspondence: T-V, 1773-1842 (Box Box 16)
    - Correspondence: W-Y, 1791-1864 (Box Box 16)
- SERIES II: BUSINESS PAPERS
  - Business Papers, 1754-1786; (14 folders) (Box Box 17)
  - Papers, 1787-1797; (11 folders) (Box Box 18)
  - Business Papers, 1798-1805; (8 folders) (Box Box 19)
  - Business Papers, 1806-1815; (10 folders) (Box Box 20)
  - Business Papers, 1816-1823; (8 folders) (Box Box 21)
  - Business Papers, 1824-1832; (8 folders) (Box Box 22)
  - Business Papers, 1833-1835; (7 folders) (Box Box 23)
  - Business Papers, 1835-1839; (8 folders) (Box Box 24)
  - Business Papers, 1840-1848; (9 folders) (Box Box 25)
  - Business Papers, 1849-1882, n. d.; (4 folders) (Box Box 26)
  - Settlement of the Stock of William Prentis, 1733-1765; (2 folders) (Box Box 26)
  - Settlement of the Stock of John Prentis, 1768-1775 (Box Box 26)
  - Settlement of the Stock of Robert Prentis, 1770-1780 (Box Box 26)
- SERIES III: LEGAL PAPERS
  - Affidavits, 1770 (Box Box 26)
  - Bills of Exchange, 1774-1775 (Box Box 26)
  - Blank Legal Forms, n.d. (Box Box 26)
  - Bonds, 1764-1809 (Box Box 26)
  - Bonds: Henry Morse, 1768, 1770-1772, 1774 (Box Box 26)
  - Bonds: Joseph Prentis, 1786-1838 (Box Box 26)
  - Circulars, Broadsides, etc., 1824-1838 (Box Box 26)
  - Claims: Joseph W. Allen & Co., 1832 (Box Box 26)
  - Claims: Samuel Beall, 1776-1782, n. d. (Box Box 26)
  - Claims: Ann Billings, 1810-1833, n. d. (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Britt vs. Britt, 1832-1835 (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Capt. Samuel Carr, Claim of Heirs in accordance with the Resolution of the Virginia Legislature, October 1777, 1849-1854 (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Coffield Estate, 1803-1821, n.d. (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Eley Estate, 1783-1794, 1821-1824 (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Gibbs Estate, 1786-1823 (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Granberry Estate, 1765-1824 (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Gray and Gorham vs. Gregory, 1818-1825 (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Hall and Godwin Estates, 1820-1835, n.d. (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Halls vs. Commonwealth, 1831 (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Hart Estate, 1792, 1803, 1839-1840, n.d. (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Holmes vs. Maxwell & Others, 1794-1796, 1822-1825 (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Hunter Estate, 1835-1837 (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Caleb Jones, 1815-1816 (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Jones Estate, 1831-1834, n.d. (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: King Estate, 1816-1817 (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Monk vs. Flynn, 1807-1812, 1816 (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: David Meade, 1801-1828 (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Aug. Moore, 1836-1837, n.d. (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Robert Prentis, 1774-1787, n.d. (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Purkin vs. Critterdon, 1808, n.d. (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Josiah Riddick, 1794, 1812-1823, n.d. (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Dr. W. S. Riddick vs. William E. Pugh, 1836-1837 (Box Box 27)
  - Claims: Rochelle vs. Rochelle, 1835-1836, n.d. (Box Box 28)
  - Claims: Shivers Estate, 1808, 1825, n.d. (Box Box 28)
  - Claims: Urquhart vs. Ricks, 1832-1836 (Box Box 28)
  - Claims: Various, 1767-1841 (Box Box 28)
  - Claims: Wills Estate, 1806, 1830, 1837-1842 (Box Box 28)
  - Claims: Young Estates, 1794-1821, n.d. (Box Box 28)
  - Collections, 1838-1839 (Box Box 28)
  - Collections: Benson & Catts, 1828-1829 (Box Box 28)
  - Collections: Bowers, 1819-1822 (Box Box 28)
  - Collections: Brown, 1823, 1827-1831 (Box Box 28)
  - Collections: Campbell, Parker, & Crocker, 1835, n.d. (Box Box 28)
  - Collections: Conroad, 1814-1815 (Box Box 28)
  - Collections: Darden, 1828-1831 (Box Box 28)
  - Collections: Garrison, 1831 (Box Box 28)
  - Collections: Gibbs, 1838-1839, n.d. (Box Box 28)
  - Collections: Hunter, 1839-1840 (Box Box 28)
  - Collections: Kyle & Paul, 1834 (Box Box 28)
  - Collections: Lawrence, 1832, 1839 (Box Box 28)
  - Collections: March, 1835, n.d. (Box Box 28)
  - Collections: Morgan & Parker, 1832-1833, n.d. (Box Box 28)
  - Collections: Mutual Assurance Society, 1832, 1838-1840 (Box Box 28)
  - Collections: Nexson, 1832 (Box Box 28)
  - Collections: Parks, 1831 (Box Box 29)
  - Collections: Pinner, 1827-1828 (Box Box 29)
  - Collections: Riddick, 1827-1832, 1837 (Box Box 29)
  - Collections: Robins, Tingley & Co., 1835 (Box Box 29)
  - Collections: Sheldon, 1826-1831, n.d. (Box Box 29)
  - Collections: Underhill, 1819-1820 (Box Box 29)
  - Collections: Webb, 1778, 1831 (Box Box 29)
  - Collections: White & Barnes, 1836 (Box Box 29)
  - Collections: Wright, 1838-1839 (Box Box 29)
  - Depositions and Papers concerning the Bigamy Case of William Green, 1758-1759 (Box Box 29)
  - Election of Robert Riddick Prentis as Judge of the Judicial Circuit of Virginia, 1894, 1903 (Box Box 29)
  - Indentures and Related, 1743 -1784 (Box Box 29)
  - Judgements, 1769 -1825, n.d. (Box Box 29)
  - Legal Memoranda ( Joseph Prentis ), 1776 -1780, n.d.; (folder 1 of 2) (Box Box 29)
  - Legal Memoranda, 1799 -1833, n. d.; (folder 2 of 2) (Box Box 29)
  - Penalties, 1835, n.d. (Box Box 29)
  - Vice-Admiralty Cases, 1770-1775, n.d. (Box Box 29)
  - Webb Family Estates, 1795-1827, n.d. (Box Box 29)
  - Will: John Blair, Williamsburg, Copy of Will, October 25, 1771 (Box Box 29)
  - Will: John Prentis, 1773-1774 (Box Box 29)
  - Will: Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1847 (Box Box 29)
  - Will: Mary Brooke Prentis, Copy of Will, February 1767 (Box Box 29)
- SERIES IV: NANSEMOND COUNTY PAPERS
  - Amendment to the Constitution of Virginia to Apportion the Representation in the House of Delegates on the Basis of White Population, 1829 (Box Box 30)
  - "Business and Reference Directory" material for Nansemond County, 1850 (Box Box 30)
  - Compositions by Joseph Prentis Webb on Suffolk and other Subjects, 1856-1857, n.d. (Box Box 30)
  - List of Slaves Emancipated by John Rawls of Nansemond County, 1835 (Box Box 30)
  - Location of Institutions in Nansemond County, 1838, 183[] (Box Box 30)
  - Meeting House Reparation, 1823 (Box Box 30)
  - Office of the Collector of Revenue of the County of Nansemond under Lemuell Riddick, 179[] (Box Box 30)
  - Office of the Surveyor of the Port of Suffolk under Thomas Swepson, 1808 (Box Box 30)
  - Office of the Surveyor of the Port of Suffolk under Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1811-1838 (Box Box 30)
  - Office of the Surveyor of the Port of Suffolk under Joseph Prentis, Jr. and Robert H. Webb: Treasury Department Circulars wlth annotations, 1817-1854 (Box Box 30)
  - Office of the Surveyor of the Port of Suffolk under Robert H. Webb, 1838-1858 (Box Box 30)
  - Office of the Surveyor of the Port of Suffolk under Robert H. Webb: Coasting Clearances and Manifests of Cargo, 1850-1855 (Box Box 30)
  - Portsmouth and Roanoke Railroad Company and Related, 1831-1837 (Box Box 30)
  - Public Sales of Property in Suffolk, 1791-1883 (Box Box 30)
  - Read's Ferry, 1825-1826 (Box Box 30)
  - Suffolk Rail Road Company, 1834-1836 (Box Box 30)
  - Topographical Descriptions of Nansemond County, 1834, n.d. (Box Box 30)
- SERIES V: GENEALOGY AND MISCELLANEOUS
  - Personal Papers of Joseph Prentis Webb II, 1913, 1932-1934 (Box Box 31)
  - Stamp Collecting, and other Hobbies of the Webb Family, 1923-1926 (Box Box 31)
  - Webb Family Genealogy: Correspondence, 1878-1939, 1951 (Box Box 31)
  - Webb Family Genealogy: Research, 1893-1905, 1937, 1952, n.d. (Box Box 31)
  - Webb Family Genealogy: Tempte - Gardner - Watkins - Anderson Branches, 1930-1937, n.d. (Box Box 31)
  - Webb Genealogy: two volumes, n.d. (Box Box 31)
- SERIES VI: BOUND VOLUMES
  - A. Accounts
    - A:1 Daybook of Andrew Meade. Includes Driver Estate and accounts with the Dismal Swamp Co., 1758-1795, 1827 (Othercontainertype Shelf)
    - A:2 Account book, 1765-1778 (Box Box 32)
    - A:3 Account book of R. Prentis, 1770-1780 (Box Box 32)
    - A:4 Account book and Garden Book of Joseph Prentis, 1775-1779, 1784-1787 (Box Box 32)
    - A:5 Account book of Joseph Prentis, Sr., 1780 (Box Box 32)
    - A:6 Expense book of Joseph Prentis, Sr. Includes expense in Williamsburg, Yorktown, Hampton, and Richmond, 1785 Oct 6 -1787 Oct 31 (Box Box 32)
    - A:7 Record book of Suffolk Customs House and list of Surveyors of Revenue, 1806-1861 (Box Box 32)
    - A:8 Domestic accountbook, 1847-1861 (Box Box 32)
    - A:9 Account book of Algernon S. Darden. Includes accounts with Mills W. Darden and Archibald Allen, and their children (his wards), 1859-1866 (Box Box 32)
    - A:10 Inventory of Real Estate owned by A. S. Darden, Jan 1892 (Othercontainertype Shelf)
  - B. Legal
    - B:1 Receipts for Legal Suit Settlements of Joseph Prentis, Sr., 1782-1787 (Box Box 32)
    - B:2 Legal Fee ledger and cash book of Joseph Prentis, Sr., 1783-1784 (Box Box 32)
    - B:3 Receipts for Legal Suit Settlements of Joseph Prentis, Sr., 1783 Mar 1 -1785 Jan 4 (Box Box 32)
    - B:4 Memorandum book of Robert Prentis; instructions for his attorney, J. Prentis, 1786 (Box Box 32)
    - B:5 Lawyer's case and fee book of Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1822-1825 (Box Box 32)
    - B:6 Lawyer's case and fee book of Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1832-1838 (Box Box 32)
  - C. Medical
    - C:1 Doctor's Daybook, 1813-1823 (Box Box 33)
    - C:2 Doctor's Daybook, 1820-1826 (Box Box 33)
    - C:3 Doctor's Daybook, 1822-1827 (Box Box 33)
    - C:4 Doctor's Daybook of R. H. Webb, 1831 Feb-Sep (Box Box 33)
    - C:5 Doctor's Daybook of R. H. Webb, 1831-1833 (Box Box 33)
    - C:6 Doctor's Daybook of R. H. Webb, 1833-1834 (Box Box 33)
    - C:7 Doctor's Daybook of R. H. Webb, 1834-1837 (Box Box 34)
    - C:8 Doctor's Daybook of R. H. Webb, 1838-1839 (Box Box 34)
    - C:9 Doctor's Daybook of R. H. Webb, 1839-1840 (Box Box 34)
    - C:10 Doctor's Daybook, 1842-1844 (Box Box 34)
    - C:11 Doctor's Daybook, 1846-1849 (Othercontainertype Shelf)
    - C:12 Doctor's Daybook, 1848-1853 (Box Box 34)
    - C:13 Doctor's Daybook, 1854-1858 (Box Box 35)
  - D. Memorandum Books and Diaries
    - D:1 Cookery and Medical Recipes of " Margaretta Prentis, Williamsburg ", 1780's (Box Box 35)
    - D:2 Medical Remedies of Joseph Prentis, 1780's (Box Box 35)
    - D:3 Diary of Exum White w/folder of loose papers from E. W.'s diary, 1809 (Box Box 35)
    - D:4 Diary and Memoranda book of Blanche Miller, 1902 (Box Box 35)
    - D:5 Memoranda book of Joseph P. Webb II - Miss Gorton's School, 1921-1922 (Box Box 35)
    - D:6 Memoranda book of Joseph P. Webb II - Episcopal High School, 1925 (Box Box 35)
  - E. Lecture Notebooks
    - E:1 Notebook of Common and State law notes from lectures by John B. Minor, 1859-1860 (Box Box 35)
    - E:2 Mathematics copybook of Joseph P. Webb I - Amelia Academy 1860, University of Virginia 1861-1862, 1860-1862 (Box Box 35)
    - E:3 Notebook of law notes from lectures by John B. Minor, 1866 (Box Box 36)
    - E:4 Vol. I Latin Literature notes of Prof. Robert H. Webb II, 1907-1908 (Box Box 36)
    - E:5 Vol.II Latin Literature notes of Prof. Robert H. Webb II, [1907-1908] (Box Box 36)
  - F. Transcripts and Letterbooks
    - F:1 Miscellaneous letters including some of William Browne, John Blair, Judge William William Nelson, and 2 Prentis wills, 1761-1829 (Box Box 37)
    - F: 2 Letters of Robert Prentis and Joseph Prentis, Sr. and Jr. Includes letters from James Monroe, 1774-1785 (Box Box 37)
    - F: 3 Letters of John Bowdoin II, 1775 (Box Box 37)
    - F: 4 Prentis Transcripts, Vol.I: Letters of Robert Prentis (1775-1804), Joseph Prentis, Sr. (1775-1826), and Joseph Prentis, Jr. (1796-1809) (Box Box 37)
    - F: 5 Letters of the Meade Family, 1782-1796 (Box Box 38)
    - F: 6 Letters of William Prentis to Robert Prentis, Joseph Prentis, Sr., and Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1784-1818 (Box Box 38)
    - F: 7 Prentis Transcripts Vol.II: Robert Saunders to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1799-1826 (Box Box 38)
    - F: 8 Letters of Peter Bowdoin to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1803-1826 (Box Box 38)
    - F:9 Letters of Joseph Prentis, Jr. to Joseph Prentis, Sr., 1805-1809 (Box Box 39)
    - F:10 Letters of Julia Pagaud, Catherine Russell, St. George Tucker, and James Semple, 1808-1825 (Box Box 39)
    - F:ll Letters of Robert Saunders, Jr. to Joseph Prentis, Jr., 1825-1851 (Box Box 39)
    - F:12 Letter book of Robert R. Prentis, 1916 (Box Box 39)
- SERIES VII: OVERSIZE
  - Letter to Geo[rge] Pitt from Arth[ur] J[en]kin[s], 1770 Apr 5 (Box Oversize)
  - Account of Henry Morse, 1770 Apr-Sep (Box Oversize)
  - Account of Henry Morse, 1772-1775 (Box Oversize)
  - "General Account of County Distillers employed in distilling spirits from Domestic materials in the third division of the fourth Survey in the district of Virginia... ", 1791 Jul 1 (Box Oversize)
  - Letter to David Meade from John Driver, 1796 Feb 21 (Box Oversize)
  - Letter to the Governors and Visitors of William and Mary College from George Blackburn (printed), [1800] (Box Oversize)
  - Letter to Joseph Prentis, Jr. from Charles H. Mallory, 1805 Feb 17 (Box Oversize)
  - Appointment of Joseph Prentis to "Surveyor and Inspector of the Revenue for the port of Suffolk in the state of Virginia " by James Monroe, 1821 Mar 10 (Box Oversize)
  - "General Statement of the Salary, fees, and emoluments of Joseph Prentis, Surveyor of the Customs for the Port of Suffolk... ", 1823 Dec 31 (Box Oversize)
  - Appointment of Joseph Prentis to "Surveyor and Inspector of the Revenue for the port of Suffolk in the state of Virginia " by Andrew Jackson, 1829 Mar 11 (Box Oversize)
  - Will of John Rawls of the County of Nanesmond (printed), 1835 Feb 21 (Box Oversize)
  - Deed granting a tract of Land in Suffolk, Nanesmond County to Robert H. Webb, 1837 Apr 1 (Box Oversize)
  - Appointment of Robert H. Webb to "Surveyor and Inspector of the Revenue for the port of Suffolk in the state of Virginia " by James K. Polk, 1846 Aug 7 (Box Oversize)
  - Coasting Manifest of the cargo on board the Schooner Charles Henry, 1850 Oct 5 (Box Oversize)
  - Coasting Manifest of the cargo on board the Schooner William H. Hunter, 1852 Apr 18 (Box Oversize)
  - Appointment of Robert H. Webb to "Surveyor and Inspector of the Revenue for the port of Suffolk in the state of Virginia " by Franklin Pierce, 1853 Jun 24 (Box Oversize)
  - Appointment of Robert H. Webb to "Surveyor and Inspector of the Revenue for the port of Suffolk in the state of Virginia " by Franklin Pierce, 1854 Mar 10 (Box Oversize)
  - Coasting Manifest of the cargo on board the Schooner William H. Hunter, 1854 Apr 10 (Box Oversize)
  - Coasting Manifest of the cargo on board the Schooner Manfred, 1854 Apr 27 (Box Oversize)
  - Coasting Manifest of the cargo on board the Schooner Ranquet, 1856 Apr 15 (Box Oversize)
  - Appointment of Robert H. Webb to "Surveyor and Inspector of the Revenue for the port of Suffolk in the state of Virginia " by James Buchanan, 1858 Apr 1 (Box Oversize)